I can make you feel, I can make you feel
I can make you feel, I can make you feel
I can make you feel, I can make you feel
If you let me
However you're feeling
I can make you feel better
Whatever you're thinking
I can make it all clearer
Don't pretend you know that you feel it
Try so hard, baby you can't conceal it
Whatever you feel inside
I can make you feel better
If that's what you want boy
Then you know where to find me
So
I can make you feel better, if you let me
I can make you feel better, if you want to
I can make you feel better, and you know you will
If that's what you want boy
Then you know where to find me
You've got to be crazy
Thinking you can resist this
Yeah you know, yeah you know
You can't help yourself
I bet you can't take it
Yeah, I'd like to just see you try
You should try, if you don't you might never know
How it tastes so good
Sweet like whipped cream
Soft and smooth
Like you felt in your dreams
So whatever your heart desires
What you need
If that's what you want boy
Then you know where to find me
So
I can make you feel better, if you let me
I can make you feel better, if you want to
I can make you feel better, and you know you will
If that's what you want boy
Then you know where to find me
Like you want to
(I can make you feel, I can make you feel)
You know you want to
(I can make you feel, I can make you feel)
Like you want to
(I can make you feel, I can make you feel)
(I can make you feel, I can make you feel)
I can make you feel better, if you let me
I can make you feel better, if you want to
I can make you feel better, if you let me
I can make you feel, I can make you feel, if you let me
I can make you feel better, like you want to
I can make you feel better, you know you want to
I can make you feel better, and you know you will
If that's what you want boy
Then you know where to find me
